excuse me
i'm trying to relax
hey kid
kid kid
just
come over here and sit down would you
what's your name mister my name is adam
you look like my grandpa said he's not
as old that's very rude
i'm adam who are you
joseph
where's your mother
she's with her boyfriend
i'm supposed to wait over here
i'm eight and three quarters mister how
old are you
mr you're boring
hey listen kid i'd like some peace and
quiet please
you're grumpy mister is that why that
woman left you on the bench
was she your girlfriend
no no she wasn't
listen um i have a girlfriend
and i'm only in the second grade
where's your girlfriend
my wife elizabeth
is gone
well where has she gone too
she's gone
gone
dead
oh
that's sad
well my girlfriend katie she's still
really young
was she a good girlfriend
katie's the best i've had
yes
elizabeth was one of a kind
why
have you ever had any other girlfriends
yesterday i brought katie a flower and
she gave me a kiss on the cheek
have you ever bought a girl flower kid
you've got a lot to learn about
relationships
have you ever looked into someone's eyes
and
had a whole conversation in an instant
laughed with someone
kept laughing until you even forgot why
you were laughing
have you ever cried i cried last night
when i said goodbye to katie
but that was because i had scraped my
knee badly
mister hmm
yes
are you going to get a new girlfriend
for all those things
no
i'm happy just by myself
i think you're grumpy
i have lots of girlfriends mister
over six
lizzy was my one and only
oh you talk about your girlfriend a lot
my wife
i love getting girlfriends mister you
should try it
there's not enough time left for me for
those kind of shenanigans
plus i thought i was a boring grumpy old
guy
nah
you're nice
well
once you stop breathing
see that pretty girl over there
i'm about to get a new girlfriend 10
seconds
there's always time
gotta go mr bye bye
nice day isn't it yeah
it's
enjoy the beautiful